<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<resources>
  <string name="AVL">AVL</string>
  <string name="Avast">Avast</string>
  <string name="DesAVL">AVL</string>
  <string name="DesAvast">Avast</string>
  <string name="DesMi">Mi</string>
  <string name="DesTencent">Tencent</string>
  <string name="Mi">Mi</string>
  <string name="Tencent">Tencent</string>
  <string name="app_name">MIUI Güvenlik Bileşenleri</string>
  <string name="avast_dialog_cloudscan"/>
  <string name="avast_dialog_dbupdate"/>
  <string name="avast_dialog_header">"Bu özellik şifrelidir ve Avast'ın sunucularına (%s) cihazınızın kimliği bu şekilde gönderilir."</string>
  <string name="avast_dialog_policy">Kullanım Şartlarına gözat</string>
  <string name="avast_dialog_title">"Avast'ın Kullanım Şartları"</string>
  <string name="avast_dialog_url">http://api.sec.miui.com/policy/proxy?p=avast&amp;l=en_US</string>
  <string name="avast_virus_type_adware_description">Bu virüs reklam içeriklidir. Otomatik olarak oluşturanın reklamlarını gösterir.</string>
  <string name="avast_virus_type_cryportor_description">The virus is a cryptor. It is a malicious software that transmitted by means of replicating itself in storage space.</string>
  <string name="avast_virus_type_dropper_description">The virus is a dropper. It carries the code that install other malicious virus.</string>
  <string name="avast_virus_type_exploit_description">The virus is an exploit. It takes advantage of a bug or vulnerability in system in order to cause unintended or unanticipated behavior.</string>
  <string name="avast_virus_type_heuristic_description">The infection is inferred by using a specific heuristic. A specific heuristic analysis says that it is a virus.</string>
  <string name="avast_virus_type_joke_description">The virus is a joke. It creates some annoying or humorous effect as a joke. It normally has less damage on the system.</string>
  <string name="avast_virus_type_pup_description">The virus is a potentially unwanted program (PUP). It is a program that may be unwanted (like spyware, adware, etc), despite the possibility that users give consen to download it.</string>
  <string name="avast_virus_type_rootkit_description">The virus is a rootkit. It is a type of software designed to hide the fact that an operating system has been compromised. It is used to gain control over the device by hiding deep inside the system. Rootkits allow viruses and malware to “hide in plain sight” by disguising as necessary files that normal antivirus software will overlook.</string>
  <string name="avast_virus_type_spyware_description">"The virus is a spyware. It a software that covertly gathers user information through the user' Internet connection without his or her knowledge."</string>
  <string name="avast_virus_type_suspicious_description">A common suspicious type. The antivirus system is trying to classify it.</string>
  <string name="avast_virus_type_tool_description">The virus is a potentially evil tool infecting by means similar to PUP.</string>
  <string name="avast_virus_type_trjan_description">Bu virus trojandır. It is a a malware designed to provide unauthorized, remote access to a user’s device. Trojans normally do not have the ability to replicate themselves like viruses; however, they can lead to other malware being installed on a machine, various data being stolen, or other malicious activities.</string>
  <string name="avast_virus_type_unknown_description">Unknown type of infection.</string>
  <string name="avast_virus_type_worm_description">Bu virüs solucandır. It is a standalone malware that replicates itself in order to spread to other devices. Takes advantage of file or information transport features of system (such like network), it can travel without any human action. Worms almost always cause at least some harm to the network.</string>
  <string name="avl_dialog_cloudscan"/>
  <string name="avl_dialog_dbupdate"/>
  <string name="avl_dialog_header">"Bu özellik cihaz kimliğini şifleyerek AVL sunucularına gönderir (%s)."</string>
  <string name="avl_dialog_policy">Gizlilik Kurallarına Gözat</string>
  <string name="avl_dialog_title">"AVL'nin Gizlilik Kuralı"</string>
  <string name="avl_dialog_url">http://api.sec.miui.com/policy/proxy?p=antiy&amp;l=en_US</string>
  <string name="default_sdcard_volume_path"/>
  <string name="hello_world">Merhaba Dünya!</string>
  <string name="menu_settings">Ayarlar</string>
  <string name="tencent_dialog_cloudscan">Çevrimiçi virüs tanımlarını kullanarak uygulama adlarını ve ayrıntıları tarayın.</string>
  <string name="tencent_dialog_dbupdate">Virus tanımlamalarını otomatik olarak güncelle</string>
  <string name="tencent_dialog_header">"Bu özellik cihaz kimliğini şifreleyerek Tencent sunucularına gönderir (%s)."</string>
  <string name="tencent_dialog_policy">Gizlilik Kuralına Gözat</string>
  <string name="tencent_dialog_title">Tencent’in Gizlilik Kuralı</string>
  <string name="tencent_dialog_url">http://api.sec.miui.com/policy/proxy?p=tencent&amp;l=en_US</string>
  <string name="title_activity_main">Esas Faaliyet</string>
</resources>
